The cartels, the black market and the fight to save a species.
Sea of Shadows is a documentary film directed by Richard Ladkani.
The vaquita, the world’s smallest whale, is nearing extinction as its habitat is destroyed  by Mexican cartels and the Chinese Mafia, who harvest the totoaba fish, the
“cocaine of the sea.” Environmental activists, the Mexican navy, and undercover investigators are fighting back against this illegal multimillion-dollar business.
Sig själv, played by Romel Eduardo Ledezma Abaroa.
Sig själv, played by Rafael Pacchiano Alamán.
Sig själv, played by Hector Capetillo.
Sig själv, played by Andrea Crosta.
Sig själv, played by Marc Davis.
Sig själv, played by Jack Hutton.
Dark Shadows is a 2012 Gothic dark fantasy comedy horror film based
on the Gothic television soap opera of the same name.
Directed by Tim Burton, the film stars Johnny Depp alongside Michelle Pfeiffer, Eva Green, Jackie Earle Haley,
Jonny Lee Miller, Chloë Grace Moretz, Helena Bonham Carter, and Bella Heathcote in a dual role.
Christopher Lee has a small role in the film, marking his 200th film
appearance and his fifth and final collaboration with Burton.
Jonathan Frid, star of the original Dark Shadows series, makes a cameo
appearance, and died shortly before the film was released.
One of the film's producers, Richard D.
Zanuck, died two months after its release.
The film had a limited release on May 10, 2012, and was
officially released the following day in North America.
It performed poorly at the United States box
office, but did well in foreign markets.
Reviews for the film were mixed; critics praised its visual style and consistent humor,
but felt it lacked a focused or substantial plot and developed characters.
The film explores themes of chinese mafia, sea shepherd,
extinction, endangered species, investigative journalism.